rsdon.net 2010-06-11

# RSdon.net - Privacy Policy

Sunday, 05 April 2009   
  
The privacy of our visitors to RSdon is important to us.

At RSdon, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit RSdon, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files  
**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include  your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons  
**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on RSdon to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Interest based advertising  
**  
Google, one of our third-party advertisers, may add a cookie to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. You can choose to opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Information you provide**  
  
Since we do not need you to register for an account, we do not possess any information, The only information you provide to us is your email address while writing comments, RSdon will never use this email address to spam you with advertisements. The only scenario in which RSdon will contact you thru the provided email address is when there is some critical update related to you comment.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time at [admin@rsdon.co.cc](mailto:admin@rsdon.co.cc)  
  
Last Updated ( Sunday, 05 April 2009 )
